govpshosting.com 2016-06-25

# Privacy Policy - GoVpsHosting

Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to the www.govpshosting.com and Govpshosting LLC and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to Govpshosting LLC include www.govpshosting.com and Govpshosting. The Govpshosting website is a news and information site. By using the Govpshosting website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement.

**Collection of your Personal Information**

We do not collect personally identifiable information from our users. We may gather personal or non-personal information in the future.

Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by Govpshosting. This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the Govpshosting website.

Govpshosting encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from Govpshosting so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. Govpshosting is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the Govpshosting website.

**Use of Cookies**

The Govpshosting website may use “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize Govpshosting pages, or register with Govpshosting site or services, a cookie helps Govpshosting to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same Govpshosting website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the Govpshosting features that you customized.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Govpshosting services or websites you visit.

**Security of your Personal Information**

Govpshosting secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure.

**Children Under Thirteen**

Govpshosting does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website.

**Opt-Out & Unsubscribe**

We respect your privacy and give you an opportunity to opt-out of receiving announcements of certain information. Users may opt-out of receiving any or all communications from Govpshosting by contacting us here:

– Web page: www.govpshosting.com

– Email: optout@govpshosting.com

**Changes to this Statement**

Govpshosting will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. Govpshosting encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how Govpshosting is protecting your information.

**Contact Information**

Govpshosting welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that Govpshosting has not adhered to this Statement, please contact Govpshosting at:

Govpshosting LLC

1395 Brickell Ave. Suite 351

Miami, Florida 33131

Email Address:

info@govpshosting.com

Effective as of Feb 3, 2016
